famousgists.com 2013-12-20

# Privacy Policy - Welcome to FamousGists News Entertainment Site

Welcome to Famousgists.com (the “Site”). Your privacy is very important to us. This statement governs our privacy policies with respect to those users of the Site (”Visitors”) who visit this the Site for  information and Visitors who subscribes to site feeds via emails on the Site and subscribe to our newsletters and make use of the various services offered by Famousgists.com  (collectively, “Services”) (”Subscribers”).

**“Personally Identifiable Information”**  refers to any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact, or locate the person to whom such information pertains, including, but not limited to, name, address, phone number, fax number, email address, financial profiles, social security number, and credit card information. Personally Identifiable Information does not include information that is collected anonymously (that is, without identification of the individual user) or demographic information not connected to an identified individual.

**What Personally Identifiable Information is collected?  **We may collect basic user profile information from all of our Visitors. We also collect the names and email addresses from our Subscribers.

**How does the Site use Personally Identifiable Information?**  We use Personally Identifiable Information to customize the Site, to make appropriate changes in the site. We may email Visitors and Subscribers about different online earning opportunities or information related to the subject matter of the Site.

**How is Personally Identifiable Information stored?**  Personally Identifiable Information collected byFamousgists.com  is securely stored and is not accessible to third parties or employees of Famousgists.com except for use as indicated above.

**Log Files and Stats**

Like most blogs this blog use log files, in this case Stat counter. This stores information such as internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring, exit and visited pages, platform used, date/time stamp, track user’s movement in the whole, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. This blog does use cookies.We use Cookies to obtain information about the preferences of our Visitors and the services they select. Some of my business partners use cookies on this site (for example – advertisers). I can’t access or control these cookies once the advertisers have set them.

**Third party links**

****This web site contains links to other web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are moving to another web site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policies may differ from ours.

**Advertisers**

This site uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when visiting this site. These third parties may collect and use information (but not your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, you can read  privacy policy of the respective advertiser.

If you wish to opt out of Advertising companies tracking and tailoring advertisements to your surfing patterns you may do so from your browser by opting out of the cookies.

We use third party ad-companies to display ads on this blog. These ads may contain cookies and are collected by the advertising companies and we do not have access to this information. We work with the following advertising companies: Clickbank. Please check the advertisers websites for respective privacy policies.

These third party advertisers uses the Doubleclick DART cookie to serve ads and you can get further information regarding the DART cookie at Doubleclick as well as opt out options at the respective advertisers’ website.

**Changes in This Policy**

We reserve the right to change this policy any time without any prior information whatsoever.We encourage our visitors to read this policy whenever they visit this site. 

1,928 total views, 8 views today
